// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "Who developed the Python programming Language",
    answer: "Guido Van Rossum",
    options: [
      "Wick Van Rossum",
      "Rasmus Lerdorf",
      "Guido Van Rossum",
      "Niene Storm"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "Which type of programming does Python support?",
    answer: "all the mentioned",
    options: [
      "Object-oriented programming",
      "structured programming",
      "functional programming",
      "all of the mentioned"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "Which of the following is the coorect extension of the python file?",
    answer: ".py",
    options: [
      ".python",
      ".pl",
      ".py",
      ".p"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "Is python code compiled or interpreted?",
    answer: "Python code is neither compiled nor interpreted",
    options: [
      "Both compiled and interpreted",
      "Python code is neither compiled nor interpreted",
      "Only compiled",
      "Only interpreted"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "Which of the followig is used to define a block of code in Python Language?",
    answer: "Indentation",
    options: [
      "Indentation",
      "Key",
      "Brackets",
      "All the above"
    ]
  },

    {
    numb: 6,
    question: "Which keyword is used to determine function in Python?",
    answer: "def",
    options: [
      "Function",
      "def",
      "fun",
      "define"
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "Which of the following can help us to find the version of python that we are currently working on?",
    answer: "sys.version(1)",
    options: [
      "sys.version(1)",
      "sys.version(0)",
      "sys.version()",
      "sys.version"
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "What does pip stands for?",
    answer: "Preferred installer Program",
    options: [
      "Unlimited length",
      "All private members must have leading and trailing underscore",
      "Preferred installer Program",
      "None of the mentioned"
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "Which of the following is the trunction division operator in Python?",
    answer: "//",
    options: [
      "|",
      "//",
      "/",
      "%"
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "Which of the following is the use of id() function in python?",
    answer: "Id returns the identity of the object",
    options: [
      "Every object doesn't have a unique id",
      "Id returns the identity of the object",
      "All of the mentioned",
      "None of the mentioned"
    ]
  },

];